<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Homepage on ~lapis/</title><link>https://lapis.self.starrypoint.me/</link><description>Recent content in Homepage on ~lapis/</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lapis.self.starrypoint.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hello, Navi.</title><link>https://lapis.self.starrypoint.me/blog/hello-navi/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lapis.self.starrypoint.me/blog/hello-navi/</guid><description>&lt;p>This was going to be a placeholder with nothing but a Serial Experiments Lain reference, but that&amp;rsquo;d be ridiculous.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How is this?</title><link>https://lapis.self.starrypoint.me/how/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lapis.self.starrypoint.me/how/</guid><description>I use the following to make this site work:
Hugo alaGeek GitHub Pages Alcohol Magic</description></item><item><title>What is this?</title><link>https://lapis.self.starrypoint.me/what/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lapis.self.starrypoint.me/what/</guid><description>This site is my personal Outernet web page, graciously hosted by the Community of Starry Point and constructed with the help of Hugo and broadcast with the help of the NETeSCAPE Innernet Self Beacon. If you live in the Innernet, please come and say hi, I welcome visitors at all times.
For any prospective reading this that are confused on what the hell I just said, don&amp;rsquo;t worry about it, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t apply to you.</description></item><item><title>When is this?</title><link>https://lapis.self.starrypoint.me/when/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lapis.self.starrypoint.me/when/</guid><description>If my timekeeping is correct, it should be sometime after 0003, or 2023.
What, you&amp;rsquo;re asking me when I get things done? Whenever. That&amp;rsquo;s my policy.</description></item><item><title>Where is this?</title><link>https://lapis.self.starrypoint.me/where/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lapis.self.starrypoint.me/where/</guid><description>I host this site on GitHub Pages, since getting consistent routing to and from the Starry Point Lighthouse is a pain. I could do it from the Tunnelvision Arcade, but I already have enough power hungry cabinets in there as it is.
If you&amp;rsquo;re asking where I live, you can find me at the Starry Point Lighthouse on the Innernet. If you&amp;rsquo;re asking for physical location, go away. I don&amp;rsquo;t take kindly to creeps.</description></item><item><title>Who is this?</title><link>https://lapis.self.starrypoint.me/who/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lapis.self.starrypoint.me/who/</guid><description>I am Lapis. I also go by Ren (renavi) as an online username. I predominantly write and worldbuild, but I sometimes do other things if I feel like it.
Outside of writing, I study Japanese. I wish to be a translator at some point in my life. An eventuality.
Lover of:
Retro consoles. Y2K aesthetic. Shitposting. The Starry Point Lighthouse. My real name will never be posted on this site. I&amp;rsquo;m sure you could figure it out if you really wanted to, though.</description></item><item><title>Why is this?</title><link>https://lapis.self.starrypoint.me/why/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lapis.self.starrypoint.me/why/</guid><description>Why do I have my own personal site? I want to. This is my own little corner of the Innernet and Outernet, and if anything, I&amp;rsquo;m glad you just stopped to say hi.
If you&amp;rsquo;re wondering why my website is structured like this, I like it. I took a few pages from NETeSCAPE, they&amp;rsquo;re nice folk.
If you wish to follow my efforts, please take a look at where I am.</description></item></channel></rss>